If she won't accept her fate,
I'll put her in her place.
This...
Mother,
what are you doing?
I must be seeing things.
Mother,
I'm playing my own daughter.
I am my mother.
What is this nonsense?
I thought
my sister was hiding some treasure.
We dug it out
and it turned out to be
just a torn painting.
Give me back my painting.
A cripple
dreaming of becoming the general's wife.
Tell Brother Ning you want
to break the engagement,
and I'll give it back.
The Emperor decreed the marriage.
Even Father can't defy it.
If you want to marry Ning Yuanci,
go tell him yourself.
Why torture me?
No!
Mom,
what are you doing?
Putting out the fire.
Why are you playing with fire?
And you,
look at your pathetic face.
You don't look like
a strong female lead at all.
Get up.
Get up!
Mom,
didn't we agree
to deal with this loser together?
I...
Ying'er,
you are
a lady from a noble family after all.
Fighting and bullying like this
is so beneath you.
I'll crush anyone
who crosses me.
Isn't that what you taught me, Mother?
You...
Why don't you learn something good?
Ying'er.
Ying'er,
I know
you don't get along with her.
But we can't use such
cheap tactics to compete with other women.
What's the point of fighting over a man
with her?
Let's fight for something useful.
She doesn't even deserve
to compete with me.
General Ning and I are in love.
If it weren't for
her status as
the eldest legitimate daughter...
How could Ning be forced to marry her?
Believe it or not,
even without me,
he wouldn't marry you.
You good-for-nothing!
You are just jealous of me.
Today, I shall drag you
into the lake with me.
I'd like to see
whether Ning saves you or me.
Somebody help! Mother!
What are you doing?
Somebody help!
Mother, what are you doing?
I can't let her be bullied anymore.
Get
out of here!
Go! Get out of here!
Go back!
Let go of me, Mother!
Go back, Mother!
Sit down.
Look at you.
You're so pretty,
smart, and capable.
You could have any man you want.
Why must you fixate
on Ning Yuanci?
It's perfectly fine
even if you keep
a few male lovers.
But there are many male lovers,
and only one Ning.
He's just
a pretty face.
He's a scheming,
ruthless control freak.
I'm telling you,
you'd better stay far away
from that kind of man.
Whether I can marry
Ning or not,
Xue Ruowan definitely can't.
Do you think I don't want to stop this
feudal arranged marriage?
You have my face,
but you didn't inherit
my brain at all.
You're really going to piss me off.
Silly girl.
Tonight,
I'll teach Xue Ruowan a lesson.
His Majesty has issued a decree.
Ning Yuanci, the General of Zhenguo,
is loyal and brave.
Xue Ruowan, daughter of the Duke of Ying,
is beautiful and intelligent.
They are a match made in heaven.
A marriage is hereby granted.
The wedding shall be held
on a chosen date.
I receive the decree.
Duke,
this matter is settled.
I think
there is no time like the present.
The wedding
will be tomorrow.
What?
Tomorrow?
The timeline has returned to
the day before the wedding.
This broken script system
is an infinite loop.
The painting in the Duke's study
has been arranged.
Please follow me to take a look.
General,
I shall go make some arrangements first.
Why not come to the residence
for a cup of tea?
We can discuss the marriage later.
Although Ning Yuanci is not the assassin,
he harbors ill intentions
toward Xue Ruowan.
It seems I must find a way
to stop this marriage.
This is the finest tea of the season.
Please have a taste, General Ning.
What?
Won't you even
show some respect
to your future mother-in-law?
General Ning,
what's
wrong?
You
drugged my tea.
Cui Hu,
I didn't.
I certainly didn't.
What did you do to our general?
I
don't
know.
Perhaps
he suffered a sudden illness.
You are conspiring to frame me.
You...
Ning,
are you alright?
Hurry!
I have an antidote here.
Hurry and take it.
Mother,
why did you ruin my plan again?
You...
Cui Hu,
Madam Xue,
I hope you can give me
a reasonable explanation
for what happened today.
I...
That Muscle-Softening Powder
is actually a drug
used for intimacy.
My mother probably wanted
to bring us together.
Please don't be mad at her anymore.
What is this?
The Muscle-Softening Powder
is not a sleeping potion,
but an aphrodisiac.
Ning,
are you really going to marry Xue Ruowan?
I was forced to marry her.
In my heart,
you are different from her.
I only want
you to belong to me.
Why is there still
a trope of a woman chasing a man?
This script should have been...
Who is it?
It's me.
I'll stop talking. I'll stop.
Since I cannot change the marriage,
tonight
I can only deal with
the assassin first.
I do not understand.
General, your marriage
with the eldest Miss Xue
is already settled.
Why are you still entangled
with the second Miss?
Xue Ruowan is weak and fragile,
suitable to be kept as a hostage.
While Xue Keying is
deeply in love with me,
making her more suitable
to be my spy.
Follow the original plan
and investigate the surroundings secretly.
See if there are
any clues about the deer totem.
Yes.
W-What
do you mean?
First you poisoned me,
and now you're stalking me.
I don't care if it's for
your daughter Xue Keying
or if you have other motives,
but don't even think about trying
to stop this marriage.
Otherwise...
Anyone who stands in my way shall die.
I am
not stopping you.
But
I have heard
that an intruder sneaked
into the manor tonight.
I am here to deliver intel to the General.
Rule of survival number one:
if you can't beat them, join them.
Desperate times call
for desperate measures.
Can't you give me
a moment of peace?
Where are you taking me?
This...
Sit tight.
Don't speak.
Remember,
a stepmother is still a mother.
This is all for your own good, you know?
Keep quiet. Not a sound.
Take a knife
for self-defense.
Take her away.
Go.
Great.
We finally caught you, you thief.
What is
going on here?
Where is Wan'er?
Madam Xue said
someone was going to assassinate Wan'er.
How did you know there was an assassin?
I
just knew it.
Now this thief has been caught.
Isn't everyone happy with this?
I'm afraid the truth isn't that simple.
Speak.
Who is your mastermind?
Why are you pointing at me?
Terrible news!
My Lady...
My Lady fell into the lake and died!
What a clever diversion.
Seize this wicked woman!
No, no, no.
General Ning, it's not true.
I did it for...
And you even tried
to assassinate our General.
I... No, I did not.
I...
Will you truly leave me no way out?
Could you please stop stabbing me here?